{
    "subject": "resource/Eugenio_Mar\u00eda_de_Hostos",
    "predicate": "ontology/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Philosopher",
    "human_readable": "Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Philosopher.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9412087798118591,
            "question": "Was Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos a scientist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8781061768531799,
            "question": "Were there any major philosophical movements that influenced Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8282836079597473,
            "question": "What was Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4329601526260376,
            "question": "What impact did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos have on society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32914355397224426,
            "question": "Can you name some famous philosophers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2853008806705475,
            "question": "What are some famous works by philosophers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2761276364326477,
            "question": "In what field did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos excel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16589801013469696,
            "question": "What are some key characteristics of a philosopher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15719471871852875,
            "question": "What makes a person interested in philosophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05522575229406357,
            "question": "How do philosophy and other disciplines intersect?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Philosopher.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5857_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes a person interested in philosophy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5857_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key characteristics of a philosopher?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5857_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what field did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos excel?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5857_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5857_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5857_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5857_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5857_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5857_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5857_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5857_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5857_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5857_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5857_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all of the documents mention Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos as a philosopher, sociologist, writer, and/or intellectual, among other professions. Therefore, the triple \"Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Philosopher\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos being a philosopher, educator, lawyer, sociologist, and writer. Therefore, the statement that \"Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was a Philosopher\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}